http://www.mha.org.uk/privacypolicy

HomeCare HomesDementia CareDementia Nursing CareNursing CareResidential CareRespite CareProfessional ReferralsWhy Choose Us?Retirement LivingRetirement Housing With 24-Hour SupportRetirement HousingRetirement VillagesNew DevelopmentsOpen DaysCommunitiesCommunities Near MeDigital CommunitiesFamilies & CarersBusiness & CorporatesHealth PartnersLocal Authority PartnersVolunteeringSuccess StoriesGet InvolvedFundraisingVolunteeringCampaigns & AppealsThe WildernessWork With UsCurrent VacanciesJobs RolesEmployment BenefitsEmployment PromiseTraining & Developmentmymha - Employee Self-ServiceNews & ViewsLatest NewsMedia CentrePolicy & InfluencingAbout UsOur StoryManagement & GovernanceMembershipsMission & ValuesPublicationsWhat Makes Us SpecialContact Us
You are here: MHA Home > Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
How we process your personal information
MHA takes your privacy seriously and is required to make available information about your rights, as well as how we process your personal information and keep it safe. Please see our privacy notices and policies below:
Privacy notices
Privacy Notice for Residents
Privacy Notice for MHA Communities Members
Privacy Notice for Relatives & Emergency Contacts
Privacy Notice for Supporters
Privacy Notice for Property Sales & Lettings
Privacy Notice for Employees, Volunteers and Board Members
Appropriate policy document
The Data Protection Act 2018 requires that we have an Appropriate Policy document that details how special category data is processed.
Data protection
MHA Data Protection Policy
Website cookies
MHA Website Cookie Policy
If you have a question about any of these documents, please contact the Data Protection Officer via:
Email: DataProtectionOfficer@mha.org.uk
Phone: 01332 221893
Post: Data Protection Officer, Methodist Homes (MHA), Epworth House, Stuart Street, Derby, DE1 2EQ
We use cookies
We use cookies to personalise content and analyse how you use our site; this helps us to provide you with the best possible experience and tailor our marketing. By clicking ‘Accept cookies’, all categories of cookies will be enabled. You can manage your cookie consent settings at any time.
Manage cookies
Accept cookies
Manage your cookie preferences
We use cookies to enhance your browsing experience and provide additional functionality. Learn more about how we use cookies on this website.
Essential cookies
Essential cookies enable the core functionality of this website. This website cannot function properly without these cookies. They can only be disabled by changing your browser preferences (please note if disabled our website may not work or show correctly on your device).
Functional cookies
Functional cookies enable us to track and save user settings (e.g. user ID, configurations) for increased user friendliness.
Performance cookies
Performance cookies collect information about how our website is used (e.g. number of visits, time spent on the site). These cookies help to optimise the website and deliver advertising that is tailored to the user.
Save settings
Accept all cookies
We use cookies to improve your experience of this website. By your continued use of this site you accept MHA's Cookie Policy.
Learn more about how we use cookies and how to change your cookie settings.
